You liked the surface when the screen was bright
Easy demo in the morning light.
You walk the halls, but you never look down at all
the heavy cables running underground. You
wanted the magic, but you hated the wire. You
couldn't handle the electric fire. The mess is
flashing on the glowing glass. You thought that
you could give yourself a pass. But the logs are
written and the ink is dry. We see the truth right
through the alibis. You only wanted the
illusion The easy version of the code You caused
a massive system fusion
And now you're pushed off the road We built a wall
you cannot break A syntax error you can't fake
You only wanted the illusion
He thought the real world was a movie screen A
simple picture in a magazine But we are the
architects, we run the clock We are the heavy
steel, the solid rock He tried to isolate the
central core But we were standing right outside
the door The mess was flashing on the glowing
glass You thought that you could give yourself a
pass But the logs are written and the ink is dry We
see the truth right through the alibi You only
wanted the illusion
The easy version of the code You caused a massive
system fusion
And now you're pushed off the road We built a wall
you cannot break A syntax error you can't fake
You only wanted the illusion
Access denied. The perimeter is locked. You
step to the line. You get blocked. The buyers are
standing shoulder to shoulder. The
temperature is dropping. Growing colder.
Access denied.
You've only wanted the illusion
The easy version of the code You caused a massive
system fusion
And now you're pushed off the road We built a wall
you cannot break A syntax error you can't fix
Access denied.
You only wanted the illusion. System locked.